♪ In the not-too-distant
future ♪
♪ way down in deep 13 ♪
♪ dr. Forrester
and tv's frank ♪
♪ were hatching
an evil scheme ♪
♪ they hired a temp
by the name of mike ♪
♪ just a regular joe
they didn't like ♪
♪ their experiment
needed a good test case ♪
♪ so they conked him
on the noggin ♪
♪ and they shot him
into space ♪
Get me down!
♪ We'll send him
cheesy movies ♪
♪ the worst we can
find-- la la la ♪
♪ he'll have to sit
and watch them all ♪
♪ and we'll monitor
his mind-- la la la ♪
♪ now keep in mind,
mike can't control ♪
♪ where the movies begin
or end-- la la la ♪
♪ he'll try to keep
his sanity ♪
♪ with the help
of his robot friends ♪
♪ robot roll call ♪
Cambot!
Gypsy!
Tom servo!
Crow!
♪ If you're wondering how ♪
♪ he eats and breathes ♪
♪ and other science
facts-- la la la ♪
♪ just repeat to yourself,
it's just a show ♪
♪ I should really
just relax ♪
♪ for mystery
science theater ♪
♪ 3000 ♪
Hello, maggots!
Welcome to boot camp
here at fort
satellite of love!
Today, we are going to do
a field strip
of one mr. Tom servo!
I'm drill sergeant
crow t. Robot!
Or sir! To you
toilet-water-guzzling
little mama's boys!
You got that, son?
- Sir, yes sir.
- I didn't hear you,
lady-britches!
I said sir, yes sir.
Can we just get on
with this, crow?
I wanna watch sisters.
You're not going nowhere,
you wussy-red cupcake!
Unless you're gonna run
home to your mama, huh?
- Ooh! Ooh, I'm scared.
- Hey, crow?
Come on.
I'm the drill sergeant here,
you toe-headed,
contact-lens-wearing
piece of toast!
Now give me the oath!
Uh, this is my robot.
There are many like it,
but this one is mine.
And what is the name
of your robot, boy?
Servo. Tom servo!
I don't believe
I was addressing you,
mayonnaise!
Why don't you just
make yourself comfortable
down there on the floor
and give me 20, corporal!
Uh, cause I can't.
Well,
now you just bought
yourself 200!
Come on, dickweed!
Uh, we'll be right back.
I heard that, pyle!
You piece of filth!
- Several pieces, actually.
- Oh.
Hello, joker.
Pyle, you are
in a world of--
hey, the mad scientists
are calling.
Outstanding.
Ah, mike.
I see you've decided
to go psycho.
Godspeed.
Anyway, our invention
exchange this week
addresses a need I'm sure
everyone can relate to.
And here's our own
tv's frank
to tell us more about it.
- Frank.
- Thank you, dr. F.
Say, don't you
just hate it when
you're suffering from
some horrible ailment,
and the only thing
that can cure you
is an organ transplant?
I hate that!
Then, what's worse,
you go to the hospital.
You have to wait
days, weeks, months,
sometimes even years
to get that organ.
That bugs the heck
out of me.
That's why we've come up
with the vend-a-gut.
The first vending machine
that dispenses
real human organs.
Now, getting a donor organ
will be as simple
as buying a snickers bar.
Now, for the sake
of this demonstration,
I took the liberty
of removing frank's liver.
- And now--
- you did?
Well, don't worry,
I also took the precaution
of inserting
your life savings
into the vend-a-gut.
Now, all you have
to do is press b-2.
And, voila,
a brand-new liver.
Let's see, b-2.
Oh, damn these things!
[Organ squishes]
Hey, this is great!
Now, all I have to do
is insert this liver
into my body.
How do I do that?
Back up to you, mike.
Well, our invention
is based upon the fact
that we, as a nation,
and as a people,
have gotten away
from our rural roots.
Heck, you know,
when I grew up,
I was surrounded
by the hustle and bustle
of a bleak urban landscape.
Oh, give it a rest, mike.
You grew up in somerset,
wisconsin.
Right, anyway, our invention
seeks to give everyone,
no matter where they live,
a taste of simple farm living.
It's fridge udders.
Now, you can milk your fridge
for everything it's worth.
It comes with four teats.
- Teats!
-He said teats!
- Wow, we can say that, too.
-Teats, teats, teats--
this one over here,
regular milk.
This one here, skim milk.
Chocolate milk.
And right here,
crushed ice.
Ow! Whoo! Hey, uh,
say, mike,
let's get drunk later
and go fridge-tipping,
what do you say?
I don't think so.
[Fridge moos]
- Steady, amana.
What do you think, sirs?
Dr. Forrester,
my body has rejected
my new liver.
Oh, here, frank,
fill this out
and put it next
to the machine.
Well, I don't wanna
wait that long!
Well then, just get another
liver from the machine!
You happen to have
$150.000 in quarters
on you, don't you?
As a matter of fact, I do.
Oh. Oh.
Anyway, mike,
your movie this week
is from the team
golan globus.
Some producers i've
wanted to inflict on you
for some time.
It stars kathy ireland,
and it's called
alien from l.a.
Alien from l.a., that's
kind of redundant, isn't it?
- Frank.
- [Frank moans]
- Teat, teat.
- [Crow coughs]
Crow, I warned you
about fridge-tipping.
- Teat teat teat--
- servo, please cut it out!
Oh great, now
we got movie sign!
Teat teat teat.
Crow, buddy, are you okay?
- Oh, yeah.
- You okay?
He's fine.
Here, get in your
thing, there.
Wanda, the creep
broke up with you
over your
answering machine.
He hates your
I just wanna know
why he broke up.
He doesn't like you.
Thanks, stacy.
You should've gone blonder.
Kiefer sutherland is hot!
- Wow.
- Oh, there's the cue card!
He's here!
[Gasps] She's nude!
Oh, yeah.
I'm so high.
[Servo hums along]
What is this,
high holiday?
Where the heck
is everybody?
Hi!
You got my message, right?
Yeah, I did, robbie.
I just wanted to--
wanted to what, harass me
about breaking up?
No, I just
wanna know why!
Well, how dare you try
to communicate with me.
What did I do wrong?
You didn't do
anything wrong, wanda.
I thought you
really liked me.
You said I was special.
So, naturally,
I wanna know why.
It's your
helium addiction.
For one thing, you
never wanna go anywhere.
I do so!
I know, two blocks,
to the beach.
You didn't want to go
on that camping trip
to the grand canyon
or rock climbing
in yosemite.
- Huh.
- Or the fourth of july
party in ensenada.
This guy's fun!
I get carsick.
I told you
I'd fly you there.
I'm scared of flying,
you know that.
- [Servo sobs]
- You're scared of everything.
Okay.
- We could've walked.
- I hate walking!
What else is wrong
with me?
Look, what's the point?
You obviously have
a serious problem.
She's emoting--
she's gonna blow!
Look out!
His nipples are shrinking.
There's only two weeks
left in august,
and I wanna salvage
some of it, all right?
Robbie, please!
We can talk about it!
Can I have
my blue dress back?
I can change!
I wanna change!
Just tell me what you
don't like about me.
Wow, she's got a lot
of pride and dignity, huh?
- Yeah, sure.
- Please, robbie!
Give me a chance!
What don't you like about me,
and I'll change.
Hey, guys, it's baywatch!
- Whoo!
- Baywatch!
- Lieutenant
what's-her-name!
--And your voice gives me
a headache, is that enough?
And you give me
whisker burns!
How come you never
told me this before?
Huh?
Why'd you even go out
with me in the first place
if I'm such a geek?
Because I'm turned on
by squeeze toys.
Wanda, I'm really sorry
I hurt you.
I didn't mean to.
It's just what I do well.
But you are who you are,
and we're just not
right for each other.
I mean, I'm right,
but you're not.
See, this should
have a brain in it.
Good-bye.
Getting dumped
in about an hour.
Yeah, sure.
Okay.
Huh, not a chest hair
between them, eh?
Nope.
Yeah, I think
we're still together.
Just another building block
to our relationship.
Saks!
Housewares is on one.
Clothing is on one.
Administration is on one.
Ah, paris in the springtime.
All this rejection
is really getting to me.
Get out of my car.
I mean, it seems
ever since I was a kid,
I've been rejected.
- Hi!
- Howard stern!
Even my own dad.
He left me.
He's an explorer, wanda.
It's his job to travel
and not be home.
For ten years?
Well, so he's
been real busy.
And what about my mom?
She's left.
She got hit by a car
and died, wanda.
She didn't have a choice.
Or did she?
Sorry.
But your mom ran
right out in front of me.
Oh, you're right.
She didn't have a choice.
But my dad did.
Where's wanda?
Where's waldo?
No one wants me.
For anything.
Sports illustrated
on the phone, cathy.
I want you, honey.
I want you to get
your butt out of this car
and come give me a hand,
I'm dying here.
See, I'm southern,
and I'm sassy.
Now kiss my grits.
Whoa... whoa...
Whoa-oh!
Whoa.
Wow! Great
production design.
I'm in conflict.
I'm experiencing
inner turmoil.
Hey, madame curie,
could you get
my fries over here?
I wonder what i'd
look like in a swimsuit.
I'm wanda saknussemm,
and I'm not gonna be
afraid to change my life.
Oh no, don't let her sing,
please, please, oh please.
This time I'm gonna do it.
This time, i'm...
Uh-oh, what was
I thinking about?
Please, god.
Mother theresa,
please hold.
Kathy's on line one.
--Anything at all, really.
Hi, kathy!
Anything.
[Servo chants]
What was that?
Golan-globus? No!
Oh no!
Kathy, you shouldn't've
gone on that diet.
Ladies, do your thighs
look like this?
Get rid of that
ugly cellulite
with a pickax!
Ugh, sometimes
I feel like that.
He's passing a stone.
Paul schaffer!
Hi, dave.
Okay, I'll take it,
but the current tenants
must go.
This is great, wanda will
never find me here.
[Laughs] Folks, thought
you'd all like a break
from the whole
kathy ireland thing.
Don't make me
come in there!
He looks like
clint howard.
Ew, what came out of me?
Interesting little...
Push this...
Bing-bong.
Who is it?
Going sideways,
mr. Saknussemm?
Maybe you could take care
of your scratching problem
before we set up the shot.
Hope I look all right for
my meeting with the sun god.
[Lightsaber hums]
Boy, it's blue in egypt.
Bluer than I remember!
I would've been satisfied
with a storage locker.
This is great!
Typical new york
five story walk up here.
Ladies and gentlemen,
survivor!
We got one,
we got one, whoo!
What kind of a thing...
Nutty thing...
Whoa!
Kiss kiss from the alien!
Dear mom,
I landed a big part
in a golan-globus film.
They're paying me $35.
Dear miss...
Sah...
Kanumin...
Senumnumanum.
The people of istanbul
reject you.
Thank you for your
interest in our country.
Neither rain nor sleet
what sleet?
That's great ganj, man.
Cool, a dc-3!
First rolled off
the assembly line
in 1936.
Oldest passenger plane
still used
for regular
commercial service.
Oh, and that's
one of the first
front-wheel-drive
ford vans--
shut up, crow. Shut up.
Hey, down in front.
Wow, that guy
ran a long way.
Turned white!
Probably a whole
different person.
Not completely different.
Wanda sak... nussemm?
No, it cleared up,
but thanks.
I can't believe it.
I bet it's my
brother-in-law.
You're wanda saknussemm?
God, no!
--Get her butt out here,
I need those four shakes.
Uh, susan,
I had the salad.
I did too, gwen.
- I'll order
the cheeseburger.
- Three burgers.
Wow, you'd figure
a supermodel
could afford
a whole shirt.
Oh, excuse me,
wanda saknussemm?
With the annoying
voice and all?
Uh, yeah,
I'm wanda saknussemm.
Special delivery
from africa.
Would you like
to sign here, please?
What a lovely
place setting, oh.
There we go.
There's a good girl.
Don't blow it, uh,
there we go.
Uh-- I did it!
That's great,
thanks very much.
Right.
There's your special sauce.
$3.25 an hour,
I'm gonna shove this job.
That sign just
really seduces you
into buying a burger,
doesn't it?
It's so small.
Oh, it's folded!
Dear...wan...da.
Oh my god.
Three syllables?
What's the matter?
My father's dead.
That's too bad,
now pick up!
Says he fell down
a bottomless pit.
Despite her lack
of flying credentials,
wanda pilots away
across the atlantic.
See, that's the beauty
of the dc-3,
its sperry gyroscopic
autopilot made it quite
- essential for--
- shut your cake hole.
Oh.
Hey! It's the blue mosque.
No, the blue mosque
is on a hill.
Have you been to istanbul?
This isn't even istanbul!
Good point.
They're bringing
stool samples to the doctor.
[Bots chuckle]
[Man whispers]
I can't hear you.
His colleagues thought
he was crazy.
They laughed at him.
They like his
observational stuff.
He dedicated
the rest of his life...
Steps! Okay,
I can handle steps.
--Self-respect.
Jerry garcia
takes her bags.
So all this time,
he's been searching
for the center of the earth.
Yes.
His excavation is down
in the basement.
Right next
to the pool table.
Hey, grizzly adams,
you waiting for a tip
or something?
- Get out of here, you.
- Hey.
- Whoa.
- Dad had a daughter!
I'm surprised to see this.
That's her
driver's license photo.
Your father cared
a lot about you.
Well...
They drugged her
to do this movie.
He sure showed it
in a weird way.
- He was a...
- Rodeo clown.
...strange man.
I've been thinking too much,
my puzzler hurts.
You look like you could
do with some rest.
Boy.
She looks like cousin itt.
It was a long trip
to africa.
Argh, come closer,
me wanda, argh.
But I'm glad
you invited me,
mr. Mahoney.
When I squint, you look
like ian anderson.
It's probably the only
chance I'll have
to get to know him.
Did they give her hash
on the way over?
He left so long ago.
Did you try
to find my dad?
Argh, get back here,
kathy gal,
where ya going, sweetie?
I go down there every day.
Look for him.
- It all seems so unlikely.
- [Servo snores]
Yeah, that's great, claude.
She's probably tired,
could you get out of the room?
I would've given anything
to see him again.
Except pancakes.
Do you need to go horsies
before you go to bed?
Well, anyway,
I've got to go.
I've got to finish tie-dying
my bedspread upstairs.
Star wolf left some
soy milk in the fridge
and some tofu.
Sweet dreams, wanda.
Got a guidebook
for greater istanbul
upstairs, if you want.
Well, I'll just
let you sleep.
And she sleeps for
a thousand years!
Haunted sun porch!
Aah! Swimsuit issue!
The whole world
smells like my eyes.
Saigon. Shucks.
I can't believe
I'm still in saigon.
Dad's yearbook!
He was voted most likely
to have an annoying
daughter!
Man's ultimate ancestors
were aliens
known as atlanteans.
Don't laugh.
No, that's
a stage direction!
They arrived on earth
with the idea
of colonizing.
But they couldn't
get green cards.
The atlanteans'
giant spaceship
served as their
floating city.
Acting's easy when you
can read your lines!
--Into the bowels
of the earth,
during a volcanic
catastrophe.
Kathy, kathy,
we're filming, kathy.
--But perhaps,
not the atlantean people.
So, dad was a delusional
psychotic.
They might still live
at the center
of the earth.
I don't get it.
What's his point?
Too heavy, dad.
Hey, it's a culture that
worships john candy.
And look, up there,
nick bockwinkle's belt buckle.
Uh, kathy, it's your dad,
I need some
toilet paper in here.
Um, this door
sounds brown.
Oh, I'm disappointed.
Not what I expected at all.
Hello?
Mr. Golan-globus, this
acting stuff is hard!
I have a reservation
for 8:30.
Oh, now this
is the kathy ireland
I know and love.
- Hunga hun--
- hey, hey hey.
- Hey, hey.
- Sorry.
Whoa!
That's a guy.
That's not.
The original
filene's basement.
Where's the store
directory?
♪ Has anybody here ♪
♪ see my old friend john? ♪
Hmm?
[Bots cough]
Janet leigh?
Why did dad have a picture
of janet leigh?
Maybe I should do that
with my hair.
You know, get a bob.
Hello?
What are you doing
behind that glass?
You look so small.
I like acting.
Especially the scenes
when I don't have to talk.
Andy? Helen?
Are you in there?
Short round,
get me my stuff.
This is kathy ireland
for coleman lanterns.
[Crow giggles]
Well, it was round
about that time
old kathy ireland went
a-burrowin' for safety
deep in the bowels
of the earth.
- The hot indiana jones
chronicles.
- Dad?
Oh, look what dad
did with the paneling.
Very nice!
[Rocks clatter]
Dad?
Look, your dad's
not responsible
for everything that
happens in the world.
Looking for mr. Good-dad.
Step out of the car, please.
[Giggles] It's fun.
That doesn't go
with my outfit.
Ew.
Ooh, bowling.
- Oh boy.
- Excuse me, pardon me.
- Oh, I'm a perfect fool.
- Criminy.
Aah!
It's so implausible, aah!
Rube goldberg.
- Mouse trap.
- Kathy, watch your mouth.
Good one, kathy.
[Wanda screams]
Aah aah aah! ...Aah.
Don't look at my
underpaaaants!
Am I in vertigo noooow?
Whoops, she pooted.
She's having a meeting with
wile e. Coyote down there.
Kathy?
Hello?
Oh poo, I'm in
the pit of hell.
Oh, now I'm gonna
have to think some more.
If this keeps up, she'll never
make it on down the shore.
Dad, is that you?
Oh, tell the prop people
to cut that out!
Oh, a plague upon
this howling.
They are louder than
the weather or our office.
Boy, you know,
that kathy ireland.
She's got a real
cute shape, doesn't she?
Yeah, yeah, kind of
reminds me of that one model.
You know, tallish one.
Um, who, elle macpherson?
No, no no no,
I'm thinking of that one,
you see her on
the magazines and all.
Oh, I know who
you're talking about.
Claudia schiffer.
No, no no, I see her
on the tv program.
You know, that you
see on the tv?
- Right, right.
- Oh!
You mean iman?
No, no no,
this one's real--
got a pretty hair thing
going, you know?
- Yeah.
- Real white teeth and such.
Oh, jill goodacre.
No no-no-no,
come on, this one
this one wears all those
fashions and whatnot.
- Yeah.
- Uh, sounds maybe like
eileen ford
or john casablancas.
Oh, I can just see her,
you know, she's in that video,
and she's got, like,
a strange name.
Uh, yeah yeah,
sort of foreign,
like, uh, maybe from germany
or england or something.
Linda evangelista?
- No.
- No no no.
Uh, carol alt?
Yasmine? Kate moss?
Kristin mcmenamy? Stop me.
No no, the name's
kind of like a bread.
I'm thinking it's like
clanilla or plantagenet.
Mm-hmm, yeah yeah yeah,
but boy is she pretty, though.
Oh, real pretty.
Well, is she, like,
70's swimsuit type?
Like cheryl tiegs-ian
or fawcett-ian?
No? Is she-- is she more
lauren hutton,
crossover type,
or beverly johnson-esque?
- No way.
- Nah, I think she's
more modern.
She's always wearing something
different, you know.
Kind of has a different
hair thing going.
Well, is she, like,
parisian waif-ish?
No eyebrows?
Androgynous type?
- Hmmm, no.
- 90's, superbrad,
house of style?
No, but I saw her once
on that talk show,
and she seemed real nice.
Christy turlington.
No no, she's in those ads,
wearing those underpants.
Oh yeah, yeah,
that's right.
Rachel hunter?
Jerry hall? Kim alexis?
No no, that band sings to her,
on that video, on tv.
Uh, cindy crawford,
niki taylor.
- No.
- Cover girl niki taylor.
I've got it, I've got it.
- Who?
- It's clara peller.
- Yeah.
That is not clara peller.
Nope, no, I remember,
that's it, clara peller.
It's not clara peller,
clara peller's
the "where's the beef"
lady, remember?
She's been dead for
a couple of years.
No, mike, I think
crow's right.
I remember seeing
that clara peller
in her underpants
on that video.
Look, we'll be back until
we straighten this out.
You did not see clara peller
in her underpants!
- I did too!
- That's impossible!
- Yow!
Yep, clara peller.
No, she's-- no.
You-- she wasn't
wetting her lips, no.
What, is this sad max?
Oh, he's from
the orkin army,
and something happened.
It won't be easy trying
to steal my claim.
Cause I'm australian.
Guess you're gonna
have to plug me for it.
Liviu ciulei directs
our town at the guthrie.
Looks easy to me!
One yank of the trigger,
and you die!
I gotta do something.
Iron my pants? No.
Redo my eyeliner? No, no,
that's not it, think!
Tell us where
the main vein is!
No.
Tell us!
Please? Come on!
Oh!
Oh, look at that!
I did something!
Home alone 3!
The destruction of jared-syn.
Oh, right, we wait all
this time to see bloomers?
Dad?
Uh, didn't you
wait on me one time?
You okay?
My boyfriend says I have
ugly hair and a weird voice--
I'm okay, are you okay?
Yeah, please don't ever
open your mouth again.
Are you gonna hurt them?
- Why not?
- I'm australian, see?
Because it's not right.
Or nice.
They'll kill me
if I don't.
You know, in australia,
my voice is as
annoying as yours.
--Mister.
Well, look, I gotta
kill somebody.
I'd better not
regret this.
Ladies and gentlemen,
we provide the scenes.
You provide
the motivation!
What's that?
What it looks like,
a troll-mule.
- It's donald pleasence.
- They killed him?
No, it's hibernating.
- Come on.
- Well, that makes it-- huh?
Where are we?
Atlantis, where else?
Can we go to cnn center?
Can I meet ted turner?
- The braves playing?
- Atlantis?
Uh-oh, I just realized
I have massive
internal bleeding.
That's impossible.
Isn't it?
Where did you
think we were?
Just trying
to look busy here.
I'm australian.
You really live
underground, don't you?
Ground.
Don't you?
Do you have
pearle-vision here?
Yeah, sure.
Of course.
I'm looking for my dad.
I left him
by the taco stand,
and now I can't find him.
And I guess
he's in atlantis.
And I don't know
where to start.
♪ Let's start
at the very beginning ♪
Well, this is the atlantis
wasteland.
Ew, he just kissed
a hamburger wrapper.
It's a day's ride.
We prize jujubes.
Do you have any pert plus?
You're not gonna leave me
here with these guys?
Look, I gotta
bounce to the city
to file my claim
before somebody else
tries to steal it.
Thanks a lot for
helping me out,
but see you later.
- Again, I'm australian.
- Hey, wait a minute!
You owe me, don't you?
Whoa, that's a switcheroo.
I could have
let them kill you.
But I didn't, did I?
No, I saved your life.
[All] Shut up!
- Please.
- Would you at least
take me to atlantis?
I mean,
that's not asking
a lot, after all.
Is it?
You wore that seashell
bikini, didn't you?
Okay.
[Car whirs]
Well, get in.
When you heard that noise,
I was turning it on, see.
You know, if gandalf had
one of those vehicles,
he'd never have died
at the hands of the balrog.
Whoa! It's a samurai.
[Wanda moans]
That was wonderful.
Whoops.
Do you need--
uh, I'm sorry, mister.
Can I give you
money for gas?
- Will that help?
- Come on.
Get in.
Or "on," actually.
Wait a second.
Get in on that side.
Would you get in over there,
please, stanley?
Tires look like
acorn squash.
- [Bots hum]
- Better put these on.
Gets kind of muddy
out here.
Oh, sorry, I wasn't australian
there for a second.
Come on, sweetheart.
- [Man mutters]
- My glasses.
Oh, there they are! Okay.
Where are you from, anyway?
Long story.
They're in schlep car.
[Servo hums]
[Wanda whimpers]
Shut up! Shut up!
...dead or alive or what.
- Shut up.
- Then I got up, so
I realized I was alive.
- Shut up.
- And I was okay,
so I started moving around,
and it was really scary.
Here, put this hose
in your mouth.
But then I stumbled onto you
and those two other guys.
And then I saved your life.
Does that
clear it up for you?
- We are devo!
- Yeah, sure.
You're from a surface
world place called l.a.,
and you're in atlantis,
looking for your dad.
Sister, you're crazy.
- Well, you're stupid.
- You think I'm lying?
I think you believe it.
Hey, do they have any
ray stevens tapes here?
I can't believe you'd think
I'd actually make up
a story like that.
You live whatever
dream you want.
None of my business.
And a pack of marlboro box
if you got them.
[Robot mutters]
Ooh, nice service
underground.
Thanks, big spender.
Boy.
- Wow, 99 for unleaded!
- Okay, come on baby.
Aah-aah-aah!
Don't ride the wild mouse,
it's not safe!
--You're asking
for trouble.
[Mike mumbles]
--You're an alien.
♪ Chicks and ducks and geese
better scurry ♪
Come on, come on,
sweetheart, come on!
Hmm?
♪ There's a world
going on ♪
♪ underground ♪
I don't wanna hear it!
Die if you like.
I'm gruff and rough!
And not ready to be loved!
[Bots sing]
It's weird, but I guess...
They always think like you
were trolls living in--
would you stop
your jabbering?
Not since tracy and hepburn.
You see, where I come from--
what is that over there?
What does it look like?
It's a matte painting!
That looks like
an underground city.
Duhr-hey.
I gotta call to make sure
the place I gotta
file my claim
is still open.
Wait here.
Okay. Wait!
I'll meet you by the
great american
hot dog experience
in an hour.
Do I love you?
I don't even know your name.
It's ted nugent. The nuge.
Guten edway.
- Wait!
- What?
Love me?
I'm wanda saknussemm.
Gus.
So what.
Uh, kathy, could you
get in the shot?
Come on, come on,
come on over.
Work with us, honey.
Hi, what's on?
--Speaking through his
representative spokesman,
denied all gossip.
Is everyone down here
a false australian?
In other news today,
many babies were
suddenly born
in zed sector.
And in sport, oceania
scored another victory
over manchester united.
[Crow sniffs]
♪ Once I had a love,
and it was a gas ♪
Come on, productions
of godspell
are punishable by death.
Good.
Guys, it's tad
from all my children!
Is the water
warm enough, wendy?
If you need me,
ask for patches.
- Who was that?
- Big trouble.
A hall monitor,
and you don't got a pass.
--Reminds me
of the wicked witch.
Extra, extra!
I will work for food.
Government
denies the truth!
I thought I had
a weird voice.
No one believes what's
printed in those papers.
Fill it with stories
about aliens every day.
You know I'm australian?
--Know what you mean.
Like little
green martians
from outer space
that landed.
Aliens, from where?
♪ Woke up,
got out of bed ♪
♪ dragged a comb
across my head ♪
What's that?
Oh, I forgot!
You don't know
what outer space is.
Until you've taken
nyquil with sudafed.
How did you live
all your life?
Well, I hung out
with warhol.
That's sad, isn't it?
I mean,
not to have seen
blue skies?
The sun?
The stars?
And malibu beach!
Well, I saw
sizzle beach u.S.A. Once.
Lay off the
surface world stuff.
She's being
very geocentric right now.
Why does everyone wear
funny makeup
and weird clothes?
Would you come on?
It's exene!
No, I think it's vanity.
Malibu beach?
It's taking kind of
a dickens-esque turn, huh?
Really, it's so
dickens-esque
it's almost dickensian.
This is kind of
a high-rent district.
Norm!
Hey, it's a nelson!
It's gunnar, I think.
We're open, I suppose.
Wow, this place
is really creepy!
They got real good
mozzarella sticks here,
so shut up.
So your girlfriend
owns this place?
Well, she owns
the franchise,
it's owned by a huge
multinational
based out of switzerland.
Hey, edgar winter,
table for two, please?
You got them
little fish crackers?
Well, look who's here.
- Who? Oh.
- How you doing, roeyis?
How do I look
like I'm doing?
Well, you look pale.
I done struck it rich,
roeyis.
That's why I'm back.
Yeah, like always.
This guy's split without
paying his bill.
Left his clothes behind.
Looks to me like
you could use them.
Well, she seems nice.
Suppose this could be
a big mining town?
Could be.
Hey, could you
put the game on?
- The game!
- The game, the big game!
How can there be
weaknesses to something
that has never happened?
This to me is good tv.
Kind of a weird
days of our lives.
I don't know any troll miner
named baz bodin.
Oh! I know, it's
abel gance's napoleon.
Not very good.
We have our sources.
Then name them, donald.
You're changing
the subject, consul.
- I'd like to assure everyone--
- kind of weird.
--That, contrary to any
rumors and gossip,
that may be circulating,
- I'm boy george.
- That we have not
captured any alien beings
from a reported
surface world.
Mr. Rogers in cabaret.
--Simply no truth
to the rumors.
This week with
david brinkley!
- Oy!
- With day-vid brinkley!
Well, back to you guys,
up in the booth.
Lying sack of crap.
[Gasps]
- Hello?
Oh! Oh...
Boing! Boing! Boing!
Boing! Boing!
I can't believe I got
an interview!
She's rebooting.
Now that killed some time.
[Electronic voice]
Test your sex appeal!
--And the unit will attempt
to improve your looks.
- She's gonna purge!
- No!
Step on pedal provided.
No, kathy, that's the bidet!
Hi, just wanted to tell you,
don't use the steam thing--
aah!
--1000 has done
all it can.
Thank you, step aside.
Hey, you look really nice.
Brought you
something to wear,
looked to me like
you needed it.
Miranda richardson
hands her an ugly coat.
Bitching.
That's really nice of you.
Couldn't stand wearing
that dress another minute.
Mm, stuarts, I can see why.
It says "all
atlantean fibers."
[Bots] Yes-- change--
change your clothes--
guys, come on.
I've never seen material
like this before.
What is it?
Uh, it's new?
Where are you from?
Um, new town?
Uh, from out of town.
It's dangerous for strangers
in atlantis these days.
People get kidnapped.
No one ever
hears of them again.
You should be careful.
You're the type that would
attract a lot of attention.
I'll be careful.
Now, can I go play?
Thanks, roeyis.
I'll be downstairs,
if you need anything.
A scene from
the children's hour.
Oh, dad.
Why would you want to come
to a place like this?
It's a planned
golf community.
I've got to find you
and get us out of here.
I think the government's doing
all right for itself, huh?
You are an alien spy
sent down by your world
to prepare an invasion
of atlantis.
I am not an alien spy
sent down by my world
to prepare an invasion
of atlantis!
I am the law here
in atlantis.
You will confess
the truth to me.
And our worlds will--
call for more
smoke, please!
[All cough]
Aah!
- No, no.
- Come on, you look great,
he looks great.
- He does look great.
- Doesn't he? Come on.
Okay, you owe me
a big favor, nelson.
- [Crow whistles]
- Shut up, crow,
and don't look at my butt.
Can we just get on
with this, please?
Okay, mccambot, just like
we practiced it,
my wild, irish ireland.
Oy, in the gaelic,
"erin go braugh-less."
Crow, don't start,
come on.
- Sorry.
- Here we go.
♪♪ [Accordion]
♪ Oh kathy, oh kathy,
my wild ireland lassie ♪
♪ you're not just
an island to me ♪
- Thank you.
- ♪ with your sparking
green eyes ♪
♪ and skin alabaster ♪
♪ you've stolen
my heart, you see ♪
♪ oh kathy, who squeaks
with the voice of an angel ♪
♪ I don't think
you're so big-a-boned ♪
♪ I'd like to come over
and roll in your clover ♪
♪ and kiss your
blarney stone ♪
Come on, big boy!
You guys, come on.
- What?
- No improvising.
Sorry, I was just
going with my feelings,
you big mush.
Let's just skip
to the chorus.
Okay.
♪ Kathy, kathy ♪
♪ my sweet lassie ♪
♪ I'll adore you ♪
♪ till the end of time ♪
That's a little predictable,
isn't it, nelson?
Come on,
just do your part.
- Okay, oh--
- no, in the voice.
♪ Oh mikey, oh mikey,
it's you that I likey ♪
♪ you're the
bitching dream ♪
♪ with those
baby blue things ♪
♪ and the stuff
that you wear ♪
♪ and your shoes
are really choice ♪
Sorry, I...
Mike, mike, it's me, tom.
Mike, no no, mike,
mike, tom here!
- Tom, mike, the chorus!
- What?
Oh, the chorus!
♪ Kathy, kathy ♪
♪ you've made me daffy ♪
♪ I will love you ♪
♪ till the end of time ♪
♪ oh kathy, compact
and delicious, young kathy ♪
♪ 'tis only for you
that I pine ♪
♪ I'll make all of your
enemies die for their sins ♪
♪ and I'll love you
till movie sign ♪
[Buzzer]
Oh, it is movie sign,
let's go!
- That was cool.
- Lovely!
Then I lost my head.
Oh, forget it.
What's a year
with no word?
Ooh!
I know what hurt you.
No, you don't!
Does she realize how
incredibly australian I am?
Huh, she must be going
to visit william burroughs.
Hmm, you know,
eventually atlantis
is gonna have to shift
to a service economy.
- Yeah.
- I'm thinking.
♪ One night in bangkok ♪
♪ makes a hard man
humble! ♪
I gotta wait until tomorrow
to file my claim.
Flow my clam?
So I figured i'll--
I'll help you
look for your dad.
Gee, thanks, gus.
I'm only doing it so's
I can get rid of you.
You're a pain in the neck,
and you're
cramping my style.
- Oy.
- Come on, let's get
something to eat.
- Oy.
- You aliens eat,
don't you?
Yeah, I'm starving.
Divorce? Bankruptcy?
Harassed by creditors?
I gotta figure out a way--
welcome to the renaissance
festival!
♪ Don't tell my heart ♪
♪ my achy breaky heart ♪
I just... don't...
It looks like
ballets tracadero.
Bet you you've never been
to a place like this before.
Well, chili's gets
pretty nuts.
Let me tell you
about our specials.
Take your order now.
I'll have the special.
What do you want?
Can't read the special--
oh, oh.
Uh,
make it two.
Coming right down.
I've gotta rub more
saliva in me hair.
Looks like
a peter greenaway set.
Tina turner
demands a table!
Yes, I want that table
over there.
Yes, that one, do you see?
Yes.
Thank you.
Any ideas on how
to find my dad?
Uh, we look for him?
Yeah, no, not yet.
I don't think too well
on an empty stomach.
He's using a mousepad
for a napkin.
Hey, it's candy slice!
Things are really
weird here.
Not like the surface
world, huh?
Oh, good one.
Right, the food's here.
I specifically said
no bacon
on my worm sandwich.
- Yuck!
- Pumpernickel!
--Gonna eat that, are you?
Hey, watch.
Screaming worms?
Mm.
- Delicious.
- Very australian.
Uh, I guess I don't need
to see the dessert tray.
My dad's a professor, gus.
And I bet he'd really
like to study you.
Hey!
Think I know someone
help you out.
You do?
Yeah, stay put,
I gotta use the phone.
Oh, that's great, gus.
He's sticking her
with the check!
♪ The farmer in the dell ♪
♪ the farmer in the dell ♪
Eh, I'm shy.
So, get me mount pilot.
Kathy smith, no!
Did I just hear a syringe?
So big-boned, 30 cc's
ought to do it!
She's deflating.
Now, see, this
is irresponsible.
They're encouraging
people to go out
and drug kathy ireland.
Now let's go burn down
the chelsea hotel.
Dad?
I'd like the number
for a...
Professor
ovid galba, please.
I can take you to your dad.
Come with me.
I'm looking for my dad.
Well, do you have
a last known address?
Um, sorry, I can't give out
that information, sir.
Live the good life
in the off-world colonies.
Oh, I think they're
in funkytown.
Funkytown.
Tonight, sam giancana
sings pagliacci!
Tonight, we have a lineup--
hey, archie rice.
--To satisfy your lusts.
[Crowd cheers]
Oh, I thought we were
beyond thunderdome.
Yeah, me too.
And only one walks out!
Now batting!
Kirby puckett!
You can't have any pudding
until you eat your meat!
How can you have any pudding
if you don't eat your meat?
[Announcer murmurs]
Wow, evening at the improv's
really changed.
On my right, smasher!
Yeah, that's me.
Hey, worms! Get your
ice-cold worms!
Get them while
they're alive!
Bloodfist 9,
the reckoning.
This is where all those
new wave bands went
when the wave was over.
That guy should not
wear horizontal stripes.
- No.
- I'm sorry.
Oh, and just where
am I supposed
to set my cole slaw now?
Your t-zone is a mess.
What is it, shank?
A girl.
I can see that.
Hey.
I want to know why you have
brought her here to me.
To mambino.
- The boss of bosses.
- [Chuckles]
I overheard her
talking, mambino.
She claims to be an al--
speak, shank.
Who did the girl
claim to be?
An actress.
An alien.
There's no such thing.
She needs to perfect
her closed-mouth smile.
Okay, I'll take
her bones elsewhere.
Did this get goofy on us?
I never said
I wasn't interested.
I implied it, sure.
I could always use another
dark girl with big bones.
Wasn't he on golden girls?
She'll cost you
500 shiny ones.
Better 400 shiny ones.
400 shiny ones--
don't push your luck, shank.
Yeah.
Whoa.
All right, just a sec, let me
get that out of the way--
- ah!
- Oh! My hinder.
I like me.
All clear.
Boy, it doesn't feel
like a tuesday, huh?
- That's the cover of tommy.
- Cool.
I have good
information to sell
about an alien wretch.
Cheryl, I love your hair.
Now, for 750 dull ones.
750 dull ones,
that's pocket change!
General rykov, please.
Just a second, just
checking your references.
I'll be right with you.
Yes?
Hello, crassus.
Sorry, I can't hear
out of this eye.
You want us to arrest
another alien?
Ay-lien.
Wow, kathy's not
nerdy anymore.
No no no.
She doesn't do much,
does she?
I don't know.
Hey, it's the band rush!
I don't trust shank.
I have to hide
the girl somewhere.
You got room at
your place, gary?
Maybe in my bed.
Kathy ireland
gets treated like
a barge full of medical waste
in this movie.
I'm mambino, boss of bosses.
Yeah, hey, boss of bosses,
you might wanna
blot your lipstick.
[Mambino mutters]
Why?
Because they buy aliens.
[Wanda giggles]
Aliens?
You think I'm an alien?
[Crow laughs]
Some people just click,
you know?
- All right.
- Let's dance!
Let's get ready
to move the mountains.
And someone get me
an eyelash curler!
- Hey!
- Oy!
- Which way?
- Over to the left
a little.
He should've picked a better
place to be a street comic.
I'm looking for
a girl with big bones.
- Yeah, who isn't, buddy?
- That way.
We represent
the lollipop guild.
Catch you later.
Welp, night life
ain't no good life,
but it's my life.
It's a theatre de la
jeune lune production.
I've lost my accent,
anyone seen it?
Accent, about this big?
Ah, general
admission bites.
Boy, a team starts doing well,
the place just fills up, eh?
Yeah.
Edway! I heard you was dead.
I'm looking for a girl
with big bones.
Where did I see them?
Whoo, doug henning goes
undercover, underground.
- Where's the girl?
- I saw them go through there.
Come on, place your bets!
Now there's the girl
with the big bones.
She's with the guy
with the small bones.
Then the danny devito
entourage arrives.
♪ Rough clowns,
out in the street ♪
♪ I wanna bite
and kiss you ♪
Gymkata!
Joe mantegna!
Sweetheart showing
some spunk.
- I hate spunk!
- Big confidence
from an alien who
walks like a troll.
Dresses like a worm,
and a voice
that gives everyone
a headache.
- Are you my boyfriend?
- I like her voice, mambino.
Paul westerberg
to the rescue.
Yay!
Edwin.
Gus!
You look terrible in plaid.
I thought you was dead.
- Well, I'm back.
- And more australian
than ever.
You never did anything
for anyone.
But you are the wind
beneath my wings.
You're too selfish
to be a hero.
Yeah.
Steve?
Joel grey in
death cabaret 5.
Go on, move.
Before I make you wish
you stayed dead.
But you see, I was never
dead in the first place.
Don't call me--
no, now he's got clown white
all over his hands.
Can't get that out.
[Gus grunts]
Kill him! Kill him!
He could at least
style his eyelashes.
Corn roll.
Here, hit me with this!
Kill him!
She's armed with
a lady thuringer.
This feels really
good in my hand.
It's firm, but it gives.
Um, are we in
an action sequence?
No.
I was just sitting there,
waiting for you,
when this woman with
too much makeup--
all right, all right,
there's no time.
Let's look up his
pant leg.
Huh? Hey, that's weird.
Oh, sorry.
--His name's
professor galba.
Is he poop deck pappy
or something?
He's moved to a district
called the pits.
- What about my dad?
- Whoa!
That'll make your
shamrock shake.
Whoa! I'm gonna get
my shillelagh.
--Go without my dad, gus.
Well, sooner or later,
they'll find you.
And if they find you,
- mm-hmm?
- They could kill you.
Oh, by the way,
I saw your butt.
We gotta go, understand?
Not without my dad, gus!
And here he is now!
Come on,
don't get separated.
♪ Da da da da-da-da
da-da-da da-da-da ♪
[Bots continue humming]
Oops.
I'll meet you at roeyis's!
Whatever may occur,
I will find you!
Whoa, a lot of loose lumber
there in atlantis.
So, why is it that
the action sequences
slow this movie down?
Eh, it hurts to be pretty.
She could really use a slip,
so atlanteans don't see
her naughty bits.
Hmm, I need campho-phenique.
Where's the food court?
Oh gee, it's susan!
If she sees me in her
dress, she'll kill me!
You know another nice thing
about atlantis?
It's all under one roof,
you can just spend
the whole day there.
She's got a tail.
She does.
[Servo sniffs]
I smell patchouli.
Oh, poopie!
There she is! There she is!
Hey, hey!
Where do you think
you're going?
Uh, can I see
the projectionist please?
- Where'd she go?
- That way!
Come on! Come along.
Middle-distance runner
suzy hamilton.
Hey, stop!
Okay.
Hold it, I think you're
gonna like this picture.
Love that bod.
I've got an idea.
I'll move the patch
to the other eye.
If shank fails us--
special agent shank.
I think I know how to find
wanda saknussemm.
Giving her
the hairy eyeball.
Lotto.
Lotto, general?
- Hello, and what do you
think of the film, hmm?
- Lotto.
Attention, shoppers, the store
will be closing in ten minutes.
I bet atlantis has
extended hours, though.
Bring what, bring what,
bring what, vina?
You know, this guy
risks overexposure.
--And lots of lotto money
will be yours.
- Big eyes, kathy.
- You will be rich
beyond your wildest dreams.
It's like the
mrs. Khrushchev club here.
Isn't that right, vina?
She's out there.
Somewhere, anywhere.
She could be standing
right next to you.
It's you! I won, I won.
All right, make a wish.
- I saw her first!
- She's mine!
Oh, and it's a scram
for kathy.
Excuse me, oh, excuse me.
Excuse me, excuse me.
[P.a. voice]
It's easy to play lotto.
Just find
the big-boned girl.
Hello, citizen.
Oh, and here comes
kid creole in hot pursuit.
[Crow hums]
Juliet, juliet!
Atchoo!
Splendid.
Well, it's the very latest
from lumeria.
Janet jackson's
stomach stand-in.
But of course, on you,
it looks absolutely smashing.
Oh no, bronson pinchot.
No, just this.
Ah, all right, well, uh,
rusty dull ones or charge?
I hate that structure store.
This is worth my walkman
and my dumb purse.
God.
She walks like jim mcmahon.
I don't care.
She's a regular sonny spoon.
Gotcha!
Ah, she's screaming
her way to safety.
Oh no, the light's
chasing after her!
Oh, pardon me.
He hurt my shoulder.
Look at that,
it's all dirty.
Hey.
Hello, babe.
- Big bopper.
- He's threatening her
with a puzzle piece.
That was real cute
back there.
Oh, not the earwax!
Go ahead, scream
all you want.
But eat all you scream.
Let me hear it.
Hey, I'm woody harrelson,
aren't I?
You ain't worth
nothing to nobody.
Speaking of worth nothing,
hello? Anyone know
what happened?
No, but it was very tense.
Kind of big-boned for
a troll, aren't you?
I'm not really a troll.
Yeah right, neither am I.
Well, you're not.
Who are you?
I'm charmin, as in style,
good looks, and panache.
Look.
I know you want me
to sweep you off your feet.
I'll love you till I die.
I want you to get
off my foot.
But I ain't got
the time right now.
I'm on my way to rob.
Boy, you really like
blue cheese, don't you.
You know,
borrow some funds.
And that gweeb back there
has made me late.
- But i--
- look,
I know it's disappointing,
- but, uh--
- I'm not mark hamill.
There'll be another time.
Another place.
Wait.
I'm not the least
attracted to you.
I'm lost, and some
people are after me.
Could you please
help me out?
I know it's a lot to ask.
- Dames.
- I told you, I'm busy.
Hey, count chocula,
clear the shot, will you?
I'm really in trouble.
Bad trouble.
Batter up!
Yes, may I help you-- aah!
She's gonna ralph!
Okay, maybe
I might help you.
It's only because
I'm a sucker
for big-boned dolls
in trouble.
Now, tell me
your problems,
and I'll decide
if I got the time.
Well, it all started
when I was ten years old--
- wait a second.
- What?
Is that really your voice?
Jeez, I'd slap
this movie if I could.
--Was about to kill me,
and then you showed up
to save my life, charmin.
You're crazy--
I wanna show you my kathy
ireland books-on-tape sometime.
--About me being an alien
from the surface world?
Now that you've gone--
hey, maybe they'll run into
spinal tap down there.
He seems like
a selfish pebble-head
who didn't care about
anybody except himself.
I used to think so.
Oh, and now you like him.
I think I understand him
a little.
Hey, hey, you
just lapped yourself.
You know, it's still
hard to go through
for someone who may
not want to see you.
She's walking like
sherman hemsley.
- You're a--
- shape-shifter.
--Very unusual girl, wanda.
And I mean,
more than because
your voice is so strange.
What exactly is wrong
with my voice?
Come on, the saloon
is this way.
Heckraiser, part two!
No!
Hey, stay away from him.
I think he might maybe
be my boyfriend maybe.
Jeez, what, did he
blue-rinse his face?
[Bots grunt, groan]
All right, kids,
something really scary!
Oh, he shouldn't fight
in his headgear.
Oh, suddenly it's the end
of highlander.
- The series, or the...
- There's too many of them.
Oh, who cares?
D'oh.
Oh, what do you use
on this floor?
It's great,
I can see myself.
What the?
There can be only one!
Nobody beats midas, nobody.
Hey, batter batter, hey!
She's a looker!
Not now, honey,
daddy's killing, please.
♪ A double murder's
waiting for you ♪
2-calorie quest.
Go tell frankenberry.
- Wait for it.
- [Man hits ground]
So, lunch?
Guess that showed him, huh?
You sure did - what?
Look, wanda,
oh, I'm adam ant.
I-- I don't know if you're
an alien or what.
But I do believe you're
here to find your father.
Hey!
I know where
her father-- oh.
For whatever reason,
the city's out to get you,
so you-- you gotta
get out of here
before it's too late
for even me to save you.
Do you mean me?
Oh, that's just
the other plot.
You get going,
I'll hold them off.
But--
it'll be easier
with you gone.
It usually is.
I might have to do something
I don't want you to see.
What, charmin?
- Never mind.
- Just squeeze me.
--Saloon is nearby.
Just up that alley.
Hide there, and i'll
meet you if I can.
Uh, my water just broke.
Will I ever see you again?
You never know, wanda.
The problems of two
second-rate actors
don't amount to a hill of beans
in this crazy underworld.
Crazy.
Another time,
another place.
Now go on, get out of here.
You taste like
goat cheese pizza.
Bye, charmin.
We'll always have
batholith.
Man, you can see
right up her skirt.
Another time,
another place.
Hey, no, aah.
Please, wait,
I'm gonna be sick.
Now, who's my love interest?
Is it the australian guy?
Oh, I know, marc singer's
gonna be in this movie.
[P.a. voice]
Once again, here
is the girl's image.
Girl answers to the name
wanda saknussemm.
Oh, that's my flight.
You can see how easy
it is she is to spot.
So find wanda and win!
A government corporation.
Well.
I guess sometimes it's just fun
to sit and people-watch.
- I guess so.
- That's another great thing
about the underworld,
- you can just sit and watch--
- shut him up.
Shut him up!
Look, eddie van halen.
There she is, general.
Uh, you can tell she's
british by her teeth.
Even if I am big-boned,
what's so wrong with that?
Doesn't make me
a bad person, does it?
I should go inside.
So, what, the movie
just take a break?
- I guess so.
- Hello?
Oh, at least
she's portable.
[Wanda screams]
No screaming
in the basement, kids.
♪ Oh wee oh ♪
♪ wee-oh whoa ♪
♪ oh wee oh ♪
How come these vehicles
never work
when they're supposed to?
He's arm-wrestling
no one there.
Where is the girl?
[Distant commotion]
Hi, gus!
Hi, wanda!
Hey, we're on our way
to the 18th tee.
Bloody hell.
She's been arrested.
- Mike!
- Mike, mike, mike!
Reach under the desk, mike!
Wow, sounds important.
Oh, it is, mike.
That's because it's the
kathy ireland fabulous
range of emotions
acting guessing game
by hasbro!
Let's play.
The first photo, mike,
portrays kathy
in a life-transforming crisis.
Mike, she has
just been informed
by native runner that
her beloved long-lost
explorer-slash-father...
- Is dead! Dead!
- Dead! Dead!
She is alone,
abandoned, bereft,
be-orphaned, beelzebub,
bea arthur, whatever.
And her face displays--
this is for 50 points,
mr. Mike nelson.
Hold on, hold on, do I have
the game right here,
you little monkeys?
I'm supposed to guess
kathy ireland's emotion, huh?
All right, I'll say, um,
soul-wrenching sadness
mixed with horror
in the face of the void.
And the answer is...
You gotta flip
that thing there.
Oh, this?
And the answer is!
Dull surprise.
Sorry, move on,
mr. Nelson.
You're 200 points
in the hole, mike,
let's move into
the lightning round.
That's right.
Begin here, mike.
Kathy decides
to transform her life.
Her emotion?
Churchillian
determination.
Dull surprise!
Next, here kathy has fallen
several hundred feet
into a hole.
Her emotion?
Uh,
shock and horror?
Dull surprise!
All right, here kathy yanks
a golf cart onto herself.
Wait, wait, wait a minute.
Wait a minute.
How many more cards do we--
hey, can you wait a minute?
How many more cards
do we have?
- 60 or 70.
- That's all.
All right, well, we'd
better get started.
I'm gonna say dull surprise.
- Dull surprise!
- Ding ding ding!
- Uh, dull surprise?
- Yes!
Dull surprise, dull surprise,
dull surprise, dull surprise,
dull surprise, boy, I'm really
racking up the points!
Dull surprise, dull surprise,
we'll be right back!
Dull surprise,
dull surprise!
I believe the aliens are
spies being sent down--
dull surprise.
Very good, very good, mike.
We must mobilize for war.
We must launch
a massive retaliation.
You're overreacting,
general.
They're here to enslave us.
- Excuse me, sorry.
- Make trolls out of us.
Didn't know this was
a read-through, I'm sorry.
I must agree with
consul crassus.
- Worf!
- The aliens are here
by accident.
Wow, anybody know how
to turn this thing off?
What do you suggest
we do, crassus?
Since the aliens arrived
accidentally, your lordship,
as you most shrewdly
observed,
maybe he could dress
for the meeting.
I suggest we help them return
to the surface world.
Your pantyhose are
on too tight, crassus.
I beg your pardon, rykov?
- Let the aliens free.
- Win cash prizes.
I for one don't want to be
reclassified as a troll.
We will release them
only if they agree
not to reveal our existence
to their world,
and no one else
is to come down.
See, I'm a trained doctor.
We have no choice
but to trust.
- Trust aliens?
- Hey, they're guest workers.
Your lordship, you cannot
possibly listen to crassus.
You know he's got
those odd tendencies.
- Oh poopie.
- And we've all been
discussing the fact
that he dyes his hair.
The general aside,
your lordship,
we are not murderers.
- Sir, actually we are.
- We cannot let them die.
Bring me the aliens.
I'll first speak to wanda.
Then decide
whether to free them
or terminate.
Coming round again.
Oh, and by the way, could
somebody get me a bucket?
I'm feeling queasy.
Are they in
captain ron's boat?
Oh, never say that again.
Come on.
It's open.
Why didn't I just get
a duplicate of that key?
- Your lordship?
- Yo?
This is the wanda.
Come here, child.
Come closer.
Pattie labelle
as amadeus.
So you are the wanda.
Yes?
I'm wanda saknussemm.
Why are you here?
Um, pass.
Where do you buy
a token around here,
for crying out loud.
You know, actually,
the transit system
in atlantis
is very efficient--
- shut up!
- It was patterned after
the metro in paris.
- Or le metro in french.
- Shut up.
What's gonna happen to her?
Lord over is trying
to decide
whether to release you
and your daughter
or to terminate your lives.
Oh. Oh!
Well, how's the look?
Frumpy but professional.
No, I mean in there.
Oh, everything
depends on wanda.
Wanda, wanda who?
I'm no explorer
- or adventurer.
- Yes you are.
- And I'm not here
to hurt your world.
- Bogus.
- I just wanna find my dad.
- Uh, where'd we find this one?
And that's why I'm here.
And for no other
reason, sir.
Oh, please.
Wanda? Got a nice big thermos
of coffee here for you.
I'm wanda saknussemm.
Don't wear it out-nussemm.
A waitress from l.a. who
should've never come here.
Here it comes.
And I just really
want to go home now.
- Hey!
- Wh-- oh.
They are going to make
brown-eyed trolls out of us.
Oh, shut up, rykov.
Zing.
Come on, say it.
Say it, here it comes.
Daddy?
Hi, wanda.
[All] Whoa! Aah!
Huh, criminy.
Now see, this is what
happens when
you try to find
the birth parents.
See?
Be home early!
Wait! What are you doing?
Papa, don't preach.
No! He's my dad.
- So you're wanda's dad.
- Yes, I am.
Well, she's gone through a lot
of trouble to find you.
Stay put while I reckon
us a way out.
How long have you
been seeing him?
So, how's your mother?
- Dead.
- Oh.
Why did you come
looking for me, wanda?
Because you're my dad.
Ah, I see, and, uh,
you can prove that?
I--
I'm sorry--
it doesn't matter now.
You're more than
I deserve.
- Yeah.
- Ew! What is that?
Gum shine.
This way, we gotta bounce!
Well then, bounce it is.
Boing boing boing boing.
Looks like gracie allen
is buried there.
It's a government
house, then?
What's the matter?
Did you forget something?
Do you have any idea
how remarkable this is?
- They're renting.
- It's a building.
No, it's not.
This is a spacecraft.
Crashed here
ten millennia ago.
- Yeah right, pops.
- From outer space.
Outer space, come on!
Old man, toys
in the attic, you know?
Is the tracking
system working?
I know where they're
headed now, general.
I'll direct you
from here, by remote.
Did you want
aisle or window?
Good work, tola.
So, crassus, I was right about
the aliens being spies.
Oh, just do your job, rykov.
Kill the girl
and her father.
- Rykov in crisis.
- I will.
And then I'll come back
for you.
I heard that!
Whoa, uh, lower
than I thought.
Unbelievable, good thing
you actually made it.
It's klandinktu!
Who is he?
He's only the bestest dad
in the whole widest world!
General, the aliens
are approaching
the outskirts of the city.
Oh yeah.
Statics at 58.
Intercept at 5.34.
Driver, head for
the outskirts of the city.
And don't take the freeway,
it's all torn up.
Actually, the atlanteans
are very supportive
of referendum bond issues.
- The highways would be--
- shut up!
The general's vehicle
has turned
for the outskirts, sir.
Follow the general.
Just don't lose her.
And pass me a sherry!
Professor saknussemm,
I have to disagree with you.
According to my data,
the incline
of the surface world
has changed--
robert fulghum thinks
he knows everything.
--The easter regions, the map
of the center of the world.
I don't doubt your
knowledge, professor.
But I've spent my life
studying and searching
for the center of the earth,
and I obviously
did find it,
and it wasn't
in this direction.
He's using someone's
feet to steer.
I have all
the equipment you need
for your ascension
to the surface of the world.
- Unt I'm a werewolf!
- It's either my way
or no way.
♪ She's a maniac
ma-- ♪
- Watch out.
- Ooh.
- Dad?
- Mrs. Lockhorn!
--Can get us back home?
We'll see, honey.
It's straight on
ahead, guten.
And don't scratch
my worm wagon.
I bet, in atlantis,
salt is really cheap.
- Huh?
- Isn't it cheap everywhere?
Dad?
Can I have a raise
in my allowance?
We now return to the big
yogurt machine.
Wow, sweetheart.
So it's not really
a bottomless pit.
- It's a topless hole.
- Pretty much.
End of the journey, eh?
Going home!
Bottom of the world, ma!
A vacation.
It's pretty impressive,
isn't it?
It's magnificent.
He's the best.
Ah, yeah, what
a beautiful day.
According
to my calculations--
we'll never work again.
--Blasted me right
up to the surface.
My god, why didn't you go?
I wanted to stay home
and watch the game.
--And he shut me down.
I was ruined and tossed out
of the university.
Ah, got your nose!
I was thrown out
of the university too,
but I wouldn't
let that stop me.
Yes, yes.
Some of us give up our dreams
more easily than others,
I suppose.
I dreamed of being
a ballerina,
but it was too impractical.
--A difference, professor,
between giving up
and leaving something
unfinished.
Here's your interplaque.
You know, I never finished
anything in my life.
Not even my australian
accent classes.
Time I did.
Hey, he's going
to the bathroom.
--Go back to roeyis.
What's rorus?
If she'll take me.
Oh, that one really
white lady.
She'll make you richer
than any mine does.
I'm a scientist!
Wanda.
Say goodbye to your
little friend.
It's time for dinner.
Goodbye, vague character!
Thanks for everything, gus!
It's time to go.
No one's going anywhere.
Till you clean up your rooms.
You blew the deal when
you tried to escape.
Yes, you blew the deal,
yes yes.
Now we have orders
to execute you.
Well, just so you
don't kill me-- hey!
I thought you
wanted us to leave.
Hey, hey, hey hey hey,
what's going on here?
I'm sorry, professor.
That's okay-- ooh!
You saw nothing.
Take the general away.
Whoa.
Bitching left hook, crassus.
[All] Just leave!
I think she's going to be a
little upset when she wakes up.
I'm joking in the form
of understatement.
I can do that,
I'm an actor.
--You get into trouble
for this?
It's a small price to pay,
now move quickly.
Hold on tight
to one another.
Get into the cyclonic
cooking thing.
I love you, honey.
[Monkey grunts]
Next time, can we
fly first class?
Anything happening yet?
Remember our deal,
professor!
- Not a word to anyone!
- So long, suckers!
We don't exist!
Well, aunty pearl,
- minnie pearl?
- Howdy!
I had this
really weird dream.
I was in
a golan-globus film.
- I went to africa.
- With shaft!
I fell down
a bottomless pit.
Into the center
of the earth.
And I ended up
in this city
called atlantis.
I was really
annoying there, too.
I found dad.
Pretty weird, huh?
Hi, honey.
I'm home.
How're you?
Oh, daddy.
It wasn't a dream.
A dream come true.
I've become conrad janis.
I love you.
Oh, a little too hard
there, honey.
And santa's coming!
Uh-huh.
Hmm, uh, maybe they
should cover that up.
- Nah.
- Ooh, still hot.
Aah! Shark! Shark!
♪ Tan, don't burn
get a coppertone tan ♪
What the?
- Oh.
- Ah.
Oh, hi.
Hey, here's a souvenir.
Hey stacy, wait up.
Hey, robbie.
- How're you doing?
- I'm here for my comeuppance.
Look, is it true
about wanda?
I heard she went to africa.
Actually took a plane
and everything.
Yeah, she actually took
a plane and everything.
- Well golly!
- Ah, I can't believe it!
Nobody in vista verde
can believe it,
including me,
including susan.
Susan, stacy.
Have you met
my trophy chick?
It's just not like her.
Are you sure this isn't
some scam to get me back?
Uh, excuse me,
my knee and your groin
have an appointment.
Why don't you
ask her yourself?
Wow, she's not
wearing glasses!
Num num num.
So, what do you do?
Hi, wanda.
Duh, overran you there, sorry.
--Take you out, and you
can tell me all about africa.
- How about you
bite me, twice?
- But why?
I still have the same hair.
Same voice.
Ah, it doesn't matter.
Believe me,
it doesn't matter.
You've changed.
Yeah, I have.
[Crow giggles]
Oh, what I wouldn't
give for all-- oh, hi.
What happened to her
in africa?
She grew up.
Men can't resist women
who fly coach to africa.
Lorenzo lamas is renegade.
She's had knee surgery.
Excuse me.
I was wondering if you
could help me out.
I'm a stranger
around here.
From another time,
another place.
Hmm, sorry,
doesn't ring a bell.
Crazy.
Phrasey? What the hell
does that mean?
Phrasey?
That's a really
generous helping
of gums we're
getting there.
Smile like a baleen whale.
She's filtering krill
through those teeth.
Hah, she lived
happily ever after.
If you call doing an occasional
guest shot on down the shore
living happily ever after.
I wouldn't.
Oh, golan-globus.
They produced lonely people
with jill clayburgh
and barbara hershey.
Did you see that, mike?
Well, no, crow,
I didn't see that
because, well, I'm a guy.
Oh. Oh really.
Yeah, well, you know,
I know you couldn't see it
because you were
watching beaches for
the hundredth time.
Shh! Shh!
--To the surface
of the world.
What?
Did that have
any relevance?
Who cares? Hey, crow,
the video store called,
they have that copy
of men don't leave they've
been saving for you.
Shh, shh.
There is no such thing
as a surface world.
And rumors of the actual
existence of aliens
are wrong, misleading,
and counterproductive
to the future
of our great city-states.
So that's irony, huh?
- Let me tell you.
- Yeah, sure is.
Hey, say, mike,
the video store called
and, uh, said your copy
of the lemon sisters
is way overdue.
Anyone who thinks
they may have
had contact with an alien,
female or older male,
should report immediately
to general rykov
at government house.
- There is a reward.
- Me!
Pretty funny, eh, guys?
Yeah, great, tom,
hey crow,
how's your new deluxe
collector's edition
of for the boys holding up?
Finally, the statement
stresses, once and for all,
aliens do not exist.
The surface world
does not exist,
and wanda saknussemm
is a mere figment
of your imagination.
Cool, a theme song.
Hey look,
paula greatbatch.
Look guys, greatbatch.
- That's really, really--
- yeah, really funny, servo.
Say, mike,
how's your exclusive
limited laserdisc
edition of yentl?
Guys, guys, guys,
cut it out.
Let's just say you're both
into really femmy movies
and leave it at that, okay?
You know, that's
a good point, tom.
By the way, could you do me
a favor and not leave your copy
of mystic pizza,
the director's cut
- lying around?
- Ooh.
Yeah, tom, and keep
your platinum edition
of the four seasons
in your own room.
Oh, sure, crow,
no problem.
As long as I don't
have to trip over
places in the heart
and the rest of your complete
sally field collection.
That's a good one, tom,
good one.
I wouldn't talk,
mrs. Nelson.
I saw you take
steel magnolias
off of crow's
sally field shelf.
Yeah, well, I know you own
the autographed script
of the goodbye girl.
Whoa. Zing.
Ahh, hmm.
Hey, hey, okay.
While I'm thinking of my next
total put-down of you guys,
let's talk about
kathy ireland.
Yeah, let's talk
about kathy ireland.
Come on, even if she
isn't a great actress,
you've got to admit,
the camera loves her.
No no, I wouldn't say that
I think it's more like,
she and the camera
are just, like,
good pals, friends,
you know?
Yeah, I mean,
she and the camera
go out and have a coffee,
maybe shop now and then.
You know, I don't think
the camera loves her.
No commitment or anything.
Well, no, you know,
I think the camera,
she and the camera
confide in each other.
You know,
they call each other,
talk to each other
on the phone all the time.
Yeah, yeah yeah,
but that's not love, nelson.
As a matter of fact,
I don't think
you even know what love is.
Oh, oh really? Mm-hmm.
Yeah, well, you know,
I'd lecture you on love,
little man, but I know
you want to get back
to your novelization
of late for dinner.
Oh, ow, boy, that
knocked me right out.
I'm out, I fold, guys,
it's too hard for me.
Great, nelson, aren't you
due at the walker
for that special screening
of six weeks?
Oh, bingo, good one there.
No, I went there, and there
was a little sign
saying it was cancelled,
because you and your pals
were there for
the cousins seminar.
- Oh!
- Whoa, that one can
leave a scar.
He's crying, mike.
- I got him.
- You got him, zinged him.
Yeah, mike, well, uh,
you set your alarm
for 3:00 am
so you watch
irreconcilable differences.
Okay, all right,
all right, yeah, well,
when I got up to watch it,
you were there crying
over the end of
don't tell her it's me.
Yeah, well, you started
a support group
because you were so
traumatized by dying young.
- Ooh.
- That's campbell scott,
right?
I wouldn't know.
- That's tough, that's tough.
Bring it back,
bring it back.
Okay, okay, well,
your dream
is to open a theater
so you can have midnight
showings of stella.
Yeah? Well, you want to start
a herb ross film festival.
[Servo whispers]
Okay, yeah, well, you paid
thousands of dollars
for the lobby cards
of always.
Yeah, well, you bought
some of the costumes from
not without my daughter.
Oh, standing eight count,
go to your corners.
- Okay.
- And resume.
All right, uh,
you called your aunt
to go see mermaids.
You rented
a safe deposit box
to keep your treasured copy
of savannah smiles.
Savannah smiles,
cute little girl, okay.
Uh, well you
started a fund drive
for a monument for
ice castles.
Yeah? Yeah?
You want a piece of me?
Yeah? You sleep with
a copy of madame sousatzka
under your pillow
every night, smart boy.
Madame sousatzka?
I challenge, servo,
let's get a ruling on that.
Madame sousatzka,
madame sousatzka.
It's, like,
shirley maclaine.
Piano teacher,
teaches young boys.
- Young boys.
- Well, I'm gonna allow it.
But careful there, crow.
Careful on these ones.
- Okay? Okay?
- Come on.
Yeah, come on, come on,
come on, what do you got?
- Give me your best.
- Wait, wait wait wait.
- What do you got?
- Whose turn is it?
Uh, it's crow's turn,
since you challenged
and lost.
- Okay, it's my turn again?
- It's crow's turn.
- Let's see here.
- Five, four,
- come on, come on.
- Three, two--
uh, you throw parties
where everyone has to dress
like a character from
fried green tomatoes!
[All] Oh.
- Okay, okay, okay, okay.
- Bring it back.
- I'm bad--
- you quote, hey!
You quote freely from
rich and famous.
There you go.
Draw?
Okay, it's a draw.
So, guys, how many times
have you see forever young?
You know, watching
this movie was like
watching a really
bad movie.
Oh, you can say that again--
what the, hey!
Hey, you know, I think
we've said everything
we can say about this movie.
Too true, too true.
So, how about a letter?
Hey, great idea!
Why don't we put that up
on still store cambot?
This one comes from
matt zimmora.
♪ How are things
in matt zimmora? ♪
Please, come on.
Crow, how come your head
never turns in front
of the movie?
That's him asking,
and when it does,
it turns right back
the other way.
How come tom servo
"dosn't" have any arms?
They move, and why
"dosn't tomservo"--
one word on tom servo--
have any eyes?
Are those slinkies
on tom servo's arms?
Why does j-i-p-s-y "jipsy"
have a flashlight
on her head?
And why doesn't gypsy
have eyes?
And then, does she,
does tom servo see?
Why does tom servo
have a bubble gum--
who do you work for, man?!
Why don't you ever show
the other robot?
Did he blow a fuse?
And the answers are.
Just cause,
and no, it doesn't.
As for me, just cause,
just cause, no,
just cause, just cause,
and we just do,
and... just cause.
What do you think, sirs?
125 thousand,
448 dollars,
25 cents.
125 thousand,
448 dollars,
and 50 cents.
Dig this, doobie brothers.
Uh, frank, what's
the number for 411?
411-- oh!
[Sobs]
Now look what you
made me do.
Now I gotta start
all over again.
[Coins spill]
♪♪ [Theme song]
[Coins continue spilling]
Yuck!